<Root>
	<Title>Match Made in Hell</Title>
	<Tagline>Love is DOOMED!</Tagline>
	<LevelSelect>Level Select</LevelSelect>
	<Level>Level </Level>
	<Settings>Settings</Settings>
	<Volume>Volume</Volume>
	<Controls>Controls</Controls>
	<RebindKeys>Rebind Keys</RebindKeys>
	<MoveLeft>Move Left: </MoveLeft>
	<MoveRight>Move Right: </MoveRight>
	<Jump>Jump: </Jump>
	<Duck>Duck: </Duck>
	<Shoot>Shoot: </Shoot>
	<Credits>Credits</Credits>
	<Back>Back</Back>
	<NewGame>New Game</NewGame>
	<LoadGame>Load Game</LoadGame>
	<Quit>Quit</Quit>
	<RejectionsList itemCount="10">
		<Item>Sorry babe, it's not me, it's you.</Item>
		<Item>This isn't gonna work out between us, but I'm sure you've got a great personality.</Item>
		<Item>I'd go out with you, but I'm gonna be sick that day.</Item>
		<Item>I'm sure you'll make some other guy, that's not me, really happy someday.</Item>
		<Item>Yikes, you looked a lot prettier from when I was at the start of the level.</Item>
		<Item>Yea, it's gonna be a no from me dawg.</Item>
		<Item>I'll call you if my plan A doesn't work out.</Item>
		<Item>If it's meant to be, it's meant to be... but just to be clear, it isn't.</Item>
		<Item>Sorry, you're just not my type. My type is attractive.</Item>
		<Item>Oh I see now. It must be girls like you that give Hell such a bad rap.</Item>
	</RejectionsList>
	<DateYesList itemCount="10">
		<Item>After much thought, I want to see what this relationship can evolve into!</Item>
		<Item>Ugh, you’re the perfect guy and I can’t see myself being with anyone else!</Item>
		<Item>Wow, you are my dream guy. I would love to go on a date with a hunk such as yourself.</Item>
		<Item>I didn’t think that I’d ever meet such a perfect guy, but here you are. I might be the luckiest demon in Hell.</Item>
		<Item>Wow, I can’t believe you massacred all of those pathetic demons just to impress me! You’ve definitely won my heart over.</Item>
		<Item>OMG, my daddy definitely wouldn't approve of you. You're perfect!</Item>
		<Item>Finally, I can stop searching! My Prince Charming has arrived.</Item>
		<Item>Finally, a man that can turn Hell into a romantic getaway. Where have you been all my life?</Item>
		<Item>OMG, you look like a guy who knows how to treat a lady. I've been waiting on my Romeo for all of eternity.</Item>
		<Item>Wow! I thought love at first sight only happened in fantasies. But I haven't been able to take my eyes off of you since you slaughtered that first demon.</Item>
	</DateYesList>
	<DateNoList itemCount="10">
		<Item>Yikes, you just come off as a blow hard. You’d would definitely not be able to handle me.</Item>
		<Item>If you wanted to win me over, you’re gonna have to do a lot better than that. Pathetic.</Item>
		<Item>Geez, and I thought Hell was bad enough as is, but now I’ve got this weak excuse for a man hitting on me? No thanks.</Item>
		<Item>Wow, Satan was right, you don’t have any shot down here. You should probably just give up now.</Item>
		<Item>You really thought that was gonna be enough to impress me? I should have just told you at the dating screen that I wasn’t interested.</Item>
		<Item>Are you kidding me? How about you try to an semi-decent demon killer before you try to be a lady killer.</Item>
		<Item>Yikes, you're about 10 pixels too short for me. Maybe you should grow a little before trying to take on a woman like me.</Item>
		<Item>Hmmm... You don't seem genuine at all. So no thanks, cause you look like you'll just reject me or something if I liked you.</Item>
		<Item>Sorry, you're just not my type. My type is someone who wears even tighter leather and is a little more douchey than you.</Item>
		<Item>Gross, you don't have nearly enough abs or hairspray to date me. I can't believe you've wasted my time.</Item>
	</DateNoList>
	<PreferencesKillList itemCount="10">
		<Item>My stupid ex was a --- demon. Honestly, I hope he burns in Hell.</Item>
		<Item>My mom was a --- demon. She always babied me and never let me do anything!</Item>
		<Item>Those dumb and ugly --- demons have always annoyed me! Like why do they even exist?</Item>
		<Item>There was this group of --- demons in my highschool that constantly harassed me and totally ruined my chances of being popular!</Item>
		<Item>My obnoxious neighbor is part of a band called Satanic Vibes and the --- Demons, and I can never sleep because of their deafening heavy metal music.</Item>
		<Item>I can't believe Lexi the --- demon won Bachelorette in Hell. She was such a two-faced skank!</Item>
		<Item>Ugh, it seems like all --- demons are the same, they're all just hotheads.</Item>
		<Item>This one time, I was on a date and he would not stop checking out other girls. Never gonna trust a --- demon ever again.</Item>
		<Item>My --- demon stepsister always wants what she can't have. She is a minx who has repeatedly tried to steal my previous boyfriends.</Item>
		<Item>This one time, I was at Alexander the Amazing --- Demon's show and he made all my friends disappear. I've had no one to talk to ever since.</Item>
	</PreferencesKillList>
	<PreferencesIgnoreList itemCount="10">
		<Item>My daddy was a --- demon. He always spoiled me and called me "Daddy’s Little Princess."</Item>
		<Item>I miss my highschool clique of --- demons. We were some of the baddest mamajamas in all of Hell.</Item>
		<Item>My favorite musician is Chance the --- Demon Rapper. His singing pierces the soul I don't have.</Item>
		<Item>My big brother was a --- demon and he taught me everything I know. He even helped me possess my first porcelain doll.</Item>
		<Item>When I was younger, I always wanted to become like Draco the --- Demon. Legend has it, he single handedly caused the Chernobyl meltdown.</Item>
		<Item>I idolize my tough-skinned --- Grandpa. He fought in the legendary Demons and Angels War and obliterated an entire battalion of cherubs.</Item>
		<Item>My favorite character in my TV show just died. He was a --- demon with the perfect balance of cynicism and ruthlessness.</Item>
		<Item>When I was in college, my professor, Dr. --- Demon, inspired me to pursure a double major in Sadism and Witchcraft. Absolutely, no regrets.</Item>
		<Item>My best friend was always there for me. If it wasn't for that amazing --- demon, Hell would be the absolute worst.</Item>
		<Item>If it wasn't for Yolanda the --- Torturer's inluence on my life on Earth, I might have ended up in Heaven. That would have been absolute torture!</Item>
	</PreferencesIgnoreList>
	<RejectionsTierList itemCount="5">
		<Item>Hopeless Mortal</Item>
		<Item>Permanent Resident of the Friend Zone (aka Hell)</Item>
		<Item>Average Douche</Item>
		<Item>Satan’s Wingman</Item>
		<Item>King of the Underworld</Item>
	</RejectionsTierList>
</Root>
